<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252"?>
<array xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	
			<listing><reference>ESL-1633</reference><price>150000</price><category>Residential for Rent</category><type>Apartment</type><city>Dubai</city><community>Dubai Marina</community><subcommunity>Dubai Marina</subcommunity><property>Ocean Heights</property><title_en>Spacious Apartment - Fully Fitted Kitchen - Sea View - Shared Pool - Shared Gym</title_en><title_ar/><description_en><![CDATA[Espace Real Estate present to you this truly fantastic high level apartment, located in the highly sought after Dubai Marina.<br><br>-2 bedrooms<br>-Marina view<br>-Fully fitted kitchen<br>-1500 sqft built up area<br>-Built in wardrobes<br>-1 parking space<br>-Balcony<br>-Excellent facilities<br>-Vacant<br><br>To discuss this property in more detail and/or to arrange a viewing, please call Asim on 050 4940897.<br><br>This 2 bedroom plus 3 bathroom apartment is open plan in layout and has a beautiful sea view which includes The Palm. With an open plan kitchen with built in appliances and open plan living room this apartment is the definition of metropolitan apartment living. The building also benefits from excellent access to the road network with easy access to Sheikh Zayed Road and is complete with excellent pool and gym facilities. The built up area of this apartment is 1,500 sqft and the property is available now.<br><br>One of the world largest, most meticulously planned waterfront developments, Dubai Marina offers the exhilaration and vibrancy of a chic urban lifestyle. Extending over 4.6 million square meters, Dubai Marina includes luxury residential buildings, shops and restaurants, children play area, swimming pools, spas, covered parking and myriad entertainment option. Dubai Marina Walk 7km-long pedestrian walkway runs along the whole development with a string of cafe and restaurants along the waterfront and dozens of luxury yachts and fancy speedboats moored up alongside.<br><br>Established in 2009, Espace Real Estate has grown from strength to strength. Today our team of experienced, professional Client Managers are here to help you, whether you are looking to buy, sell or lease a property. We understand that the process can be stressful and time consuming which is why we go that extra mile to help you. As well as offering a large portfolio of properties throughout Dubai, the team also offers advice on the latest market trends, useful knowledge on your chosen community as well as a full array of home services. We provide an extensive array of marketing opportunities to our clients ranging from our quarterly magazine "EspaceXtra" through to the largest Open House events in Dubai, and everything in between.<br>Whether you are looking to buy, sell or lease an apartment or villa, our professional Client Managers will provide a professional, informative, honest service to you every step of the way, offering a seamless service from beginning to end.<br>Office location: Unit 2702 and 2703 Marina Plaza, Dubai Marina, Dubai UAE<br>Tel no: 04 306 9999.]]></description_en><description_ar/><sqft>1500</sqft><bedroom>2</bedroom><bathroom>3</bathroom><agent_name>Asim Sheikh</agent_name><agent_email>asim@espace.ae</agent_email><agent_number/><agent_info/><photo_url_1>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view21292456100.jpg</photo_url_1><photo_url_2>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view1.jpg</photo_url_2><photo_url_3>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view2.jpg</photo_url_3><photo_url_4>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view4.jpg</photo_url_4><photo_url_5>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view5.jpg</photo_url_5><photo_url_6>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view6.jpg</photo_url_6><photo_url_7>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view7.jpg</photo_url_7><photo_url_8>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view8.jpg</photo_url_8><photo_url_9>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view9.jpg</photo_url_9><photo_url_10>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/lettings/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-amazing-2-bedroom-apartment-on-a-high-level-with-marina-view-NT1-2639.jpg</photo_url_10></listing>
			<listing><reference>ES-2579</reference><price>9500000</price><category>Residential for Sale</category><type>Villa</type><city>Dubai</city><community/><subcommunity/><property/><title_en>Prime location, Golf Course View, Fully Upgraded, Immaculate Condition, Close to the Town Centre</title_en><title_ar/><description_en><![CDATA[New to the market with Espace Real Estate is this fully upgraded type 13 in an excellent location in Meadows 4. This fantastic five bedroom villa has marble flooring throughout and sits on a great plot with the added benefit of a private swimming pool. This property is very well maintained by the owners.<br><br>-5 bedrooms plus maids<br>-Fully upgraded<br>-BUA: Approximately 3,998 sqft<br>-Plot: Approximately 6,650 sqft<br>-Golf course view<br>-Private swimming pool<br>-Close to the lake<br>-2 parking spaces<br>-Vacant on transfer<br><br>The Meadows, part of Emirates Living, is one of the most popular and prestigious places to live in Dubai. Close to Sheikh Zayed Road and Dubai Marina, this self-contained community has excellent amenities ranging from schools, to retail outlets in its mini retail centres, community swimming pools and picturesque lakes. The Meadows is popular with families and young professionals looking to escape the city life but still be close by. Well known for its spacious villas ranging from 3-6 bedrooms, residents can also enjoy their own private garden along with 24 hour security. There is also the Emirates Golf Club and Montgomerie Golf Club close by for those who enjoy relaxing over a game of golf.<br><br>Established in 2009, Espace Real Estate has grown from strength to strength. Today our team of experienced, professional Client Managers are here to help you, whether you are looking to buy, sell or lease a property. We understand that the process can be stressful and time consuming which is why we go that extra mile to help you. As well as offering a large portfolio of properties throughout Dubai, the team also offers advice on the latest market trends, useful knowledge on your chosen community as well as a full array of home services. We provide an extensive array of marketing opportunities to our clients ranging from our quarterly magazine "EspaceXtra" through to the largest Open House events in Dubai, and everything in between. Whether you are looking to buy, sell or lease an apartment or villa, our professional Client Managers will provide a professional, informative, honest service to you every step of the way, offering a seamless service from beginning to end.<br><br>Office location: Unit 2702 & 2703 Marina Plaza, Dubai Marina, Dubai, UAE.<br>Tel no: 04 306 9999]]></description_en><description_ar/><sqft>3998</sqft><bedroom>5</bedroom><bathroom>4</bathroom><agent_name>Osman Dada</agent_name><agent_email>osman@espace.ae  </agent_email><agent_number>+971508753909</agent_number><agent_info/><photo_url_1>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-7464249070.jpg</photo_url_1><photo_url_2>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-1.jpg</photo_url_2><photo_url_3>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-2.jpg</photo_url_3><photo_url_4>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-3.jpg</photo_url_4><photo_url_5>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-4.jpg</photo_url_5><photo_url_6>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-5.jpg</photo_url_6><photo_url_7>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-6.jpg</photo_url_7><photo_url_8>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-7.jpg</photo_url_8><photo_url_9>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-8.jpg</photo_url_9><photo_url_10>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-9.jpg</photo_url_10><photo_url_11>http://www.espacecrem.com/Espace-CREM/floor_plan/Villa 13.JPG</photo_url_11><photo_url_12>http://www.espacecrem.com/gallery/images/sales/properties/villas-apartments/large/espace-fully-upgraded-independent-villa-with-golf-course-views-11.jpg</photo_url_12></listing>
			
	</array>		